Finding Aid for University of Michigan. Dept. of Medicine and Surgery Theses, 1851-1878
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Medical Theses
  - Class of 1866
    - Holton, Samuel Mills (d. 1920), "Enteric Fever", 1866 (Reel 16)
    - House, Alfred Burge (d. 1909), "Inflammation", 1866 (Reel 16)
    - Hume, Edward Morris (d. 1877), "Exclusive Methods of Practice", 1866 (Reel 16)
    - Hurd, Henry Mills, "The Heat of the Human Body", 1866 (Reel 16)
    - Jenkins, John Fletcher (d. 1906), "Opium", 1866 (Reel 16)
    - Jennings, Augustus F., "Hernia", 1866 (Reel 16)
    - Johnston, John Keys (d. 1903), "Medicine, the Central Profession", 1866 (Reel 16)
    - Jones, William Brown (d. 1869), "Typhoid Fever", 1866 (Reel 16)
    - Kibbie, Hamilton Carlos (d. 1918), "Advantages of Making Medicines Palatable", 1866 (Reel 16)
    - Kingham, Joseph (d. 1912), "Sanguis", 1866 (Reel 16)
    - Kinmont, Thomas Cato (d. 1918), "The Nature and Treatment of Paralysis", 1866 (Reel 16)
    - Knapp, Charles Edgar, "Pathological Conditions of the Blood", 1866 (Reel 16)
    - Knapp, William Barnabas (d. 1914), "Circulation", 1866 (Reel 16)
    - Lowell, Julian Virinoldi (d. 1893), "Diagnosis of Diseases of the Heart", 1866 (Reel 16)
    - McCracken, James Washington (d. 1921), "Malarial Diseases", 1866 (Reel 16)
    - McFerran, William, "The Medical Profession", 1866 (Reel 16)
    - McLean, James Brown (d. 1876), "Pathological Anatomy of Tumors", 1866 (Reel 16)
    - McPherson, George William, "The Vital Force", 1866 (Reel 16)
    - Manly, Allen Clark (d. 1919), "Hygiene", 1866 (Reel 16)
    - Marsh, Hiram Whitfield, "Bilious Remmittant Fever", 1866 (Reel 16)
    - Martin, William Henry (d. 1884), "Scorbutus", 1866 (Reel 16)
    - Matthews, Luther Increase (d. 1918), "Hernia", 1866 (Reel 16)
    - Mills, Hiram Rollin, "Animal Heat", 1866 (Reel 16)
    - Moore, Hosea Hartwell (d. 1913), "Milk Sickness", 1866 (Reel 16)
    - Morse, Herbert Augustine (d. 1915), "Cerebro Spinal Meningitis", 1866 (Reel 16)
    - Odell, Robert Woolsey (d. 1916), "Yellow Fever", 1866 (Reel 16)
    - Pelton, Arthur Montgomery, "Pneumonia", 1866 (Reel 16)
    - Porter, Robert Thomas (d. 1922), "Opium, its Natural History, Physiological and Therapeutical Effects", 1866 (Reel 16)
    - Post, James Alexis, "Chronic Dislocations", 1866 (Reel 16)
    - Price, Oscar Jay, "Physical Diagnosis", 1866 (Reel 16)
    - Reed, Warren Franklin (d. 1913), "Function of the Spinal Chord", 1866 (Reel 16)
    - Reilly, Bernard Sylvester (d. 1867), "Cerebro-Spinal Meningitis", 1866 (Reel 16)
    - Robbins, David Peter, "Hygiene: its Utility and Neglect", 1866 (Reel 16)
    - Robinson, William Hayley (d. 1914), "Gonorrhea", 1866 (Reel 18)
    - Roome, John S. (d. 1919) "Typhoid Fever", 1866 (Reel 18)
    - Russell, Charles, "Cholera", 1866 (Reel 18)
    - Sculley, Myron Clark (d. 1899), "Intermittent Fever", 1866 (Reel 18)
    - Sellers, Amos (d. 1879), "Hygiene", 1866 (Reel 18)
    - Smith, Elias (d. 1902), "Sleep", 1866 (Reel 18)
    - Stocking, Charles Henry, "Tubercular Meningitis", 1866 (Reel 18)
    - Vanderburgh, David Williams (d. 1910), "Fractures of the Femur", 1866 (Reel 18)
    - Weir, Robert Melville (d. 1905), "Phthisis Pulmonalis", 1866 (Reel 18)
    - Wells, Charles Russell, "The Mutual Influence of the Mind and Body in Disease", 1866 (Reel 18)
    - White, James Smith (d. 1902), "Cathartics", 1866 (Reel 18)
    - Wight, Wesley W. (d. 1917), "Inflammation", 1866 (Reel 18)
    - Wilber, Albert Mortimer (d. 1917), "Pleurisy", 1866 (Reel 18)
    - Young, John Francis (d. 1886), "The Importance of a Liberal Preliminary Education to the Student of Medicine", 1866 (Reel 18)
  - Class of 1867
    - Allen, Giles Bertram (1842-1911), "Physiology of the Blood", 1867 (Reel 18)
    - Arensberg, Louis Frederick, "The Spleen", 1867 (Reel 18)
    - Aylsworth, Homer Elhanan (d. 1885), "Medical Quicksands or Sources of Professional Obliquity", 1867 (Reel 18)
    - Bates, Charles (d. 1881), "Dropsy", 1867 (Reel 18)
    - Beebe, William Smith, "The Vital Stimuli", 1867 (Reel 18)
    - Benjamin, Henry Rawson (d. 1893), "Foeticide", 1867 (Reel 18)
    - Bigelow, Edward Elisha, "Nutrition", 1867 (Reel 18)
    - Bonesteel, Samuel Aquila (d. 1902), "The Healing Process, and Diseases of the Healing Process", 1867 (Reel 18)
    - Booth, Robert (d. 1910), "The History and Progress of Medicine and Surgery", 1867 (Reel 18)
    - Bradshaw, Augustus C. D. (d. 1905), "Indigestion", 1867 (Reel 18)
    - Brown, Samuel Houston (d. 1882), "Cerebro-spinal System, Anatomically and Physiologically Considered", 1867 (Reel 18)
    - Bullock, Zenas (d. 1882), "The Natural History of Disease", 1867 (Reel 18)
    - Carpenter, Dewitt Clinton (d. 1868), "Opium", 1867 (Reel 18)
    - Chavey, Pierre Jacques (d. 1903), "Cardiac Auscultation", 1867 (Reel 18)
    - Cheever, Byron William (d. 1888), "Medica Scientia Ante Christum", 1867 (Reel 19)
    - Collett, Theodore Alfred (d. 1903), "Counter-irritation", 1867 (Reel 19)
    - Creamer, John Milton, "Enteric, or Typhoid Fever", 1867 (Reel 19)
    - Davis, Francis Flanegin (d. 1902), "Diphtheria", 1867 (Reel 19)
    - Davis, Rhodes D., "Nutrition", 1867 (Reel 19)
    - Dill, Daniel Mountfert (d. 1911), "Opium", 1867 (Reel 19)
    - Dumon, Dan L. (d. 1909), "Fibrous Tumors of the Uterus", 1867 (Reel 19)
    - Dunlap, Archibald Stewart (d. 1919), "The Medical Profession-its Dignity and Progress", 1867 (Reel 19)
    - Eaton, Thomas Jefferson (d. 1906), "Incompatibles in Medicine", 1867 (Reel 19)
    - Edwards, Daniel Mann (d. 1919), "Mind and Medicine", 1867 (Reel 19)
    - Fanning, Fred Walter (d. 1906), "Pneumonia", 1867 (Reel 19)
    - Farrington, Stephen Sonora (d. 1872), "Modus Operandi of Medicines", 1867 (Reel 19)
    - Foote, Albert Edward (d. 1895), "Diabetes", 1867 (Reel 19)
    - Garlock, Alonzo W. (d. 1898), "The Study of Medicine", 1867 (Reel 19)
    - Girard, Joseph Basil (d. 1918), "La vie de l'Enfance et ses Relations a la Pathologie", 1867 (Reel 19)
    - Granger, George Hess (d. 1905), "Inguinal Hernia", 1867 (Reel 19)
    - Guinan, James (d. 1900), "Phthisis Pulmonalis-Tuberculosis", 1867 (Reel 19)
    - Haines, Reuben (d. 1879), "Diarrhea", 1867 (Reel 19)
    - Harcourt, Robert Hamilton (d. 1879), "Typhoid Fever", 1867 (Reel 19)
    - Hawley, John Frank (d. 1870), "Mortification", 1867 (Reel 19)
    - Hill, Harvey Daniel (d. 1913), "Hygiene", 1867 (Reel 19)
    - Hood, John Samuel (d. 1915), "The Influence of the Mind over the Body", 1867 (Reel 19)
    - Hotchkiss, William Wallace (d. 1873), "The Circulation of the Blood", 1867 (Reel 19)
    - Hurd, Edward Homer (d. 1921), "Anesthetics", 1867 (Reel 20)
    - Jackson, George Washington (d. 1910), "Pneumonia", 1867 (Reel 20)
    - Johnson, Colonel D. (d. 1876), "Typhoid Fever", 1867 (Reel 20)
    - Johnson, Henry (d. 1915), "Physiological and Therapeutical Effects of Alcohol", 1867 (Reel 20)
    - Jones, George Sproson (d. 1897), "Cerebrospinal Meningitis", 1867 (Reel 20)
    - Jones, Nathan Davis, "Intermittent Fever", 1867 (Reel 20)
    - Kezartee, Ira Young (d. 1914), "Digestion", 1867 (Reel 20)
    - Little, William, "Urinology", 1867 (Reel 20)
    - Lyon, David Randall (d. 1892), "Cerebro-spinal Meningitis", 1867 (Reel 20)
    - McGaughey, James Brown (d. 1908), "Hygiene", 1867 (Reel 20)
    - McLean, Donald Alexander, "Influences Modifying the Action of Medicines", 1867 (Reel 20)
    - Matthews, Frederick Lawson (d. 1891), "Asiatic Cholera", 1867 (Reel 20)
    - Mendenhall, Ryan Goudy (d. 1907), "Malaria", 1867 (Reel 20)
    - Miner, Selden, "Strumous Ophthalmia", 1867 (Reel 20)
    - Moore, George Oramel, "Fractures of the Lower Extremity, with the Best Methods of Extension and Counter Extension", 1867 (Reel 20)
    - Mott, John Sabert, "Syphilis", 1867 (Reel 20)
    - O'Brien, Dennis Cornelius (d. 1922), "Fractures", 1867 (Reel 20)
    - Ostrom, Sylvester Charles Jones, "Dothinenteritis", 1867 (Reel 20)
    - Parker, Henry Clay (d. 1918), "Opium", 1867 (Reel 20)
    - Prichard, Lewis (d. 1920), "Conditions Necessary to Healthy Nutrition", 1867 (Reel 20)
    - Read, Ira Beman (d. 1897), "Correlation of Physical and Vital Forces", 1867 (Reel 20)
    - Revenaugh, Aurelius O. (d. 1908), "Mental Influences", 1867 (Reel 21)
    - Reynolds, George Rensselaer (d. 1904), "General Considerations in Medical Diagnosis", 1867 (Reel 21)
    - Robbins, Jerome John (1841-1921), "The Lymphatic System", 1867 (Reel 21)
    - Rogers, James S., "Cold Water as a Medical Agent", 1867 (Reel 21)
    - Roome, William Frederick (d. 1921), "Epidemic Cholera", 1867 (Reel 21)
    - Scammon, Ezra Albert (d. 1919), "A Surgical View of the Aplastic Diathesis", 1867 (Reel 21)
    - Scott, Alexander Hamilton (d. 1915), "The Red Corpuscles of the Blood", 1867 (Reel 21)
    - Simpson, Robert Stuart, "Blood", 1867 (Reel 21)
    - Smith, Sumner Timothy (d. 1892), "Yellow Fever", 1867 (Reel 21)
    - Smith, Thomas Kerrins (d. 1908), "The Nervous System and its Sympathies", 1867 (Reel 21)
    - Southworth, John Willard (d. 1889), "Medical Common Sense", 1867 (Reel 21)
    - Speirs, William Wallace (d. 1908), "Generation", 1867 (Reel 21)
    - Sperry, Lyman Beecher, "Therapeutic Observation", 1867 (Reel 21)
    - Stephens, Alexander, "Hernia", 1867 (Reel 21)
    - Stickel, Jacob (d. 1918), "The Eye", 1867 (Reel 21)
    - Thompson, Benjamin (d. 1887), "Placenta Praevia", 1867 (Reel 22)
    - Tingley, Daniel Webster (d. 1875), "Cell Life", 1867 (Reel 22)
    - Treat, Joseph Augustus (d. 1919), "Epilepsy", 1867 (Reel 22)
    - Tyler, John Bennett (d. 1915), "The Human Hand", 1867 (Reel 22)
    - Vaughan, William Emery (d. 1880), "Lead Colic", 1867 (Reel 22)
    - Walker, Jackson (d. 1917), "Sympathy", 1867 (Reel 22)
    - Wiest, John (d. 1891), "Sympathy", 1867 (Reel 22)
    - Wilkinson, Warren Gray (d. 1877), "The Red Globules of the Blood", 1867 (Reel 22)
    - Wines, Henry Hebbard (d. 1868), "Erysipelas", 1867 (Reel 22)
  - Class of 1868
    - Adams, Carlos James (d. 1911), "Puerpural Fever", 1868 (Reel 22)
    - Aikman, Robert, "Indigestion", 1868 (Reel 22)
    - Alleman, Andrew Ashton (d. 1872), "Pneumonia", 1868 (Reel 22)
    - Alvord, Austin White (d. 1915), "Valvular Disease of the Heart", 1868 (Reel 22)
    - Armstrong, Rolla Silas, "Etiology", 1868 (Reel 22)
    - Ballard, Ezra Hardin (d. 1900), "Spermatorrhaea", 1868 (Reel 22)
    - Bartlett, Jeremiah Cook (d. 1917), "Medical Ethics", 1868 (Reel 22)
    - Berry, Charles Hazard (d. 1902), "Influences Modifying the Action of Medicines", 1868 (Reel 22)
    - Bogart, John Henry, "Blood-letting", 1868 (Reel 22)
    - Burrell, Dwight Robbins (d. 1910), "Our Moral Materia Medica", 1868 (Reel 22)
    - Burton, Isom (d. 1921), "Pneumonitis", 1868 (Reel 22)
    - Cleveland, Edmund Francis Xavier (d. 1919), "Physiology of Touch and Smell", 1868 (Reel 22)
    - Clizbe, Stephen Henry (d. 1908), "Coxalgia", 1868 (Reel 22)
    - Cochran, Isaac Newton (d. 1916), "Intermittent Fever", 1868 (Reel 22)
    - Cooper, Aaron W. (d. 1922), "The Blood", 1868 (Reel 22)
    - Corey, Allen Lilbern, "Opium", 1868 (Reel 22)
    - Corey, Frank (Francis) Edwin, "Mind and Medicine", 1868 (Reel 22)
    - Cox, Gardner (d. 1912), "The Persistence of Motion", 1868 (Reel 23)
    - Cox, Henry Major (d. 1902), "Microscope", 1868 (Reel 23)
    - Davison, Edward C. (d. 1874), "Food", 1868 (Reel 23)
    - Edmonds, Samuel (d. 1910), "Typhoid Fever", 1868 (Reel 23)
    - Evans, Selby (d. 1869), "Vis Medicatrix Natura" (sic), 1868 (Reel 23)
    - Fuller, Frederic Gurley (d. 1888), "Forces Engaged in the Circulation of Blood", 1868 (Reel 23)
    - Garner, Charles Lucius (d. 1870), "Placenta Previa", 1868 (Reel 23)
    - Gifford, William Riley, "Infancy and its Management", 1868 (Reel 23)
    - Goodwin, Andrew Jackson (d. 1894), "Magnum Donum Dei: Opium", 1868 (Reel 23)
    - Goodyear, Miles Dennison (d. 1913), "Influences Modifying the Actions of Medicines", 1868 (Reel 23)
    - Gorsuch, Silas N. (d. 1907), "The Progress of Medical Science, as Illustrated by the Discovery of the Circulation of the Blood", 1868 (Reel 23)
    - Griffin, Clark Chandler, "Inflammation", 1868 (Reel 23)
    - Griffin, Walter S., "Life and Death", 1868 (Reel 23)
    - Grubbs, John Cloud (d. 1878), "Sub Coelum, or Life in the Open Air, its Therapeutical Uses", 1868 (Reel 23)
    - Harris, Richard Fuller (d. 1904), "Blood Disks, Their Origin, History, &c (sic)...", 1868 (Reel 23)
    - Haskell, Howard Malcolm (d. 1919), "Indigestion", 1868 (Reel 23)
    - Hawes, Jesse (d. 1901), "Inflammation", 1868 (Reel 23)
    - Hill, Malcolm (d. 1897), "The Anatomy and Physiology of the Blood", 1868 (Reel 23)
    - Hill, William James (d. 1918), "The True or Ideal Physician and his Manifest Duty", 1868 (Reel 23)
    - Hood, John (d. 1919), "The Physician's Ideal", 1868 (Reel 23)
    - Johnson, Levi Ormsby (d. 1915), "Mental Influences", 1868 (Reel 23)
    - Jones, Jonathan Knight (d. 1874), "Scirrous or Hard Cancer", 1868 (Reel 23)
    - Kapp, John (d. 1911), "Pneumonia", 1868 (Reel 23)
    - Kirk, William Hamilton, "Senile Gangrene", 1868 (Reel 23)
    - Knapp, Granville Liberty, "Typhoid Fever", 1868 (Reel 24)
    - Lanterman, George Saladay (d. 1900), "Influences Modifying the Effects of a Medicine", 1868 (Reel 24)
    - Lincoln, Charles Henry (d. 1909), "Enteric Fever", 1868 (Reel 24)
    - Lyons, Mason Russell (d. 1871), "Coxarius Morbus", 1868 (Reel 24)
    - McMillan, Dugald (d. 1918), "The Blood", 1868 (Reel 24)
    - Marshall, Frederick Dey (d. 1919), "Auscultation", 1868 (Reel 24)
    - Martin, Elton Thomas (d. 1891), "Hygiene", 1868 (Reel 24)
    - Maynard, James B., "Flame", 1868 (Reel 24)
    - Mitchell, William Francis (d. 1909), "Typhoid Fever", 1868 (Reel 24)
    - Morison, John Portuous (d. 1909), "Criminal Abortion", 1868 (Reel 24)
    - Nichols, Harrison A. (d. 1909), "Imponderables", 1868 (Reel 24)
    - North, John, "Trichiniasis", 1868 (Reel 24)
    - O'Neill, Alexander (d. 1920), "Delirium Tremens", 1868 (Reel 24)
    - Ormsby, Byron J., "Diphtheria", 1868 (Reel 24)
    - Parr, Thomas Simpson (d. 1907), "Healthy Nutrition", 1868 (Reel 24)
    - Patten, Anthony Dimock (d. 1917), "Syphilis", 1868 (Reel 24)
    - Phelps, Sidney Pearl (d. 1880), "Enteric Fever", 1868 (Reel 24)
    - Phillips, Horace Henry, "Traumatic Tetanus", 1868 (Reel 24)
    - Pratt, Henry Rice (d. 1894), "Hysteria", 1868 (Reel 24)
    - Prichard, Isaac Watson, "Thermometer; Its Utility in the Diagnosis, Prognosis, and Treatment of Diseases", 1868 (Reel 24)
    - Riggs, John Upton (d. 1911), "Anesthetics", 1868 (Reel 24)
    - Sabin, George Gleason (d. 1911), "Syphilis", 1868 (Reel 24)
    - Sanford, George Hoyt (d. 1914), "The Pathology, Cause and Treatment of Chronic Dysentery", 1868 (Reel 24)
    - Scovill, Bela Philander (d. 1917), "Diphtheria", 1868 (Reel 24)
    - Shaw, William Henry (d. 1915), "Food", 1868 (Reel 25)
    - Short, Uriah Merwin (d. 1899), "Pneumonitis", 1868 (Reel 25)
    - Slaght, Andrew (d. 1915), "Inflammation and its Products", 1868 (Reel 25)
    - Smith, Stillman Hiram (d. 1890), "Anesthetics", 1868 (Reel 25)
    - Spohn, Jacob Charles (d. 1906), "Therapeutical Application of the Sulphites", 1868 (Reel 25)
    - Starkey, John C. (d. 1879), "The Kidney, its Function, and Excretion", 1868 (Reel 25)
    - Stewart, Thomas Harris (d. 1912), "The Hypodermic Administration of Medicines", 1868 (Reel 25)
    - Test, Erastus (d. 1917), "The Liver and its Functions", 1868 (Reel 25)
    - Thomas, Henry Franklin (1843-1912), "Pneumonia", 1868 (Reel 25)
    - Van Horn, Abraham Leonard, "Rubeola", 1868 (Reel 25)
    - Vrooman, Charles Wesley (d. 1881), "Syphilis", 1868 (Reel 25)
    - Watson, Eltham (d. 1879), "Tobacco", 1868 (Reel 25)
    - Webb, Frank (d. 1875), "Acute Lobar Pneumonia", 1868 (Reel 25)
    - Wilder, Flavius Myron (d. 1892), "Hydrated Oxide of Ethyl", 1868 (Reel 25)
    - Williams, John Knox (d. 1914), "Avoidable Causes of Disease", 1868 (Reel 25)
    - Woodman, Eli (d. 1892), "Effects of Blisters on the Young Subject", 1868 (Reel 25)
  - Class of 1869
    - Ambrose, Hannibal Luther (d. 1902), "Scarlatina", 1869 (Reel 25)
    - Barnes, George Palmer (d. 1885), "Influences Modifying the Effects of Medicines", 1869 (Reel 25)
    - Barton, Ira, "The Blood, its Anatomy and Physiology", 1869 (Reel 25)
    - Besley, John Mortimer (d. 1890), "Cataract", 1869 (Reel 25)
    - Binkley, William Grabill, "Vis Medicatrix Naturae", 1869 (Reel 25)
    - Bloomfield, Edmund Marshall (d. 1913), "Typhoid Fever", 1869 (Reel 25)
    - Boise, Eugene Philip, "Nature as a Physician", 1869 (Reel 26)
    - Borrowman, Andrew (d. 1880), "Opium", 1869 (Reel 26)
    - Bostater, Andrew Jackson, "Mucous Membrane", 1869 (Reel 26)
    - Bowers, Jacob Eton (d. 1922), "The History, Pathology and Treatment of Insanity", 1869 (Reel 26)
    - Brainerd, Henry Clark, "Antiquity of Medicine", 1869 (Reel 26)
    - Brown, Francis Richard (d. 1898), "A Treatise on Hernia, Inguinal and Femoral", 1869 (Reel 26)
    - Burtch, William Edmond (d. 1903), "Elimination", 1869 (Reel 26)
    - Cantwell, Alonzo William (d. 1899), "The Hand", 1869 (Reel 26)
    - Carrier, Elbert Emmons (d. 1870), "The Mucous Membrane of the Alimentary Canal", 1869 (Reel 26)
    - Castle, Frederick (d. 1910), "Neuro-pathology", 1869 (Reel 26)
    - Champlin, Alfred Henry (d. 1907), "The Oath of Hippocrates", 1869 (Reel 26)
    - Chase, Henry Wonton (d. 1889), "The Pathology of the Blood", 1869 (Reel 26)
    - Claflin, Nelson Henry (d. 1916), "The Obstetric Forceps and Their Use", 1869 (Reel 26)
    - Cody, Charles Bissel (d. 1908), "Medical Geography", 1869 (Reel 26)
    - Cole, Theodore (d. 1922), "Physiology of the Liver", 1869 (Reel 26)
    - Creagh, Jasper, "The Circulation of the Blood", 1869 (Reel 27)
    - Crummer, Benjamin Franklin (d. 1907), "Dysentery", 1869 (Reel 27)
    - Davison, Calvin Knox (d. 1908), "Epidemic Dysentery", 1869 (Reel 27)
    - Dewey, Richard Smith, "Force in its Vital Manifestations", 1869 (Reel 27)
    - Dodge, James Shaw, "Dislocations", 1869 (Reel 27)
    - Dodge, John Richardson (d. 1917), "The Mind, Its Relations to the Brain", 1869 (Reel 27)
    - Drake, Horace Leander (d. 1902), "The Venereal Disease", 1869 (Reel 27)
    - Ellis, Mordecai Cleveland (d. 1878), "Sulphate of Quinia", 1869 (Reel 27)
    - Everett, William Edward (d. 1920), "Physiology of the Pancreas", 1869 (Reel 27)
    - Ford, James Mitchell, "Carbolic Acid", 1869 (Reel 27)
    - George, William Henry (d. 1912), "Anaesthesia", 1869 (Reel 27)
    - Gillam, Samuel Edward (d. 1908), "Malignant Growths", 1869 (Reel 27)
    - Glasgow, Robert David, "The History, Action and Uses of Opium", 1869 (Reel 27)
    - Golden, John (d. 1922), "Antimonii et Potassae Tartras", 1869 (Reel 27)
    - Graham, Hugh Crawford (d. 1871), "Puerperal Convulsions", 1869 (Reel 27)
    - Green, Franklin Leroy (d. 1907), "Veratrum Veride", 1869 (Reel 27)
    - Greenfield, Robert Newton (d. 1923), "Puerperal Convulsions", 1869 (Reel 27)
    - Hagle, Peter Noble (d. 1889), "Sleep or Somnia", 1869 (Reel 27)
    - Hamilton, William Bruce, "Foetal Life", 1869 (Reel 28)
    - Hatfield, David Starrett (d. 1919), "The Heart", 1869 (Reel 28)
    - Hendryx, Truman Cornelius (d. 1909), "Cause and Cure of Disease", 1869 (Reel 28)
    - Hershey, Byron Delbert (d. 1885), "The Influences Modifying the Effects of Medicines", 1869 (Reel 28)
    - Hollon, LeGrand Hale, "Anaemia", 1869 (Reel 28)
    - Jarvis, Wesley John (d. 1912), on nerves, 1869 (Reel 28)
    - Kelly, Edward Henry (d. 1912), "Puerperal Convulsions", 1869 (Reel 28)
    - Kennedy, Charles H. (d. 1902), "Indigestion", 1869 (Reel 28)
    - Kier, Harry (Henry) McBride, "Spermatorrhaea", 1869 (Reel 28)
    - Langford, George Washington (d. 1897), "Etiology", 1869 (Reel 28)
    - Leslie, James Daniel (d. 1881), "Transfusion", 1869 (Reel 28)
    - Lewis, Didamus, "Pleurisy", 1869 (Reel 28)
    - Loomis, Goodwin Thomas (d. 1891), "Water and its Medical Properties", 1869 (Reel 28)
    - Lyon, Octavius C. (d. 1894), "The Cause and Treatment of Tuberculosis", 1869 (Reel 28)
    - McDowell, George Fancette, "Opium", 1869 (Reel 28)
    - McKenna, Levi Franklin (d. 1892), "The Anatomy and Physiology of the Stomach", 1869 (Reel 28)
    - McKenzie, James Dugald (d. 1908), "Typhoid Fever", 1869 (Reel 28)
    - Maltbie, William Francis (d. 1905), "Nerve Function", 1869 (Reel 28)
    - Marsh, Charles Franklin (d. 1908), "Alcoholic Stimulants! Are They Good Adjuncts in the Treatment of Disease?", 1869 (Reel 28)
    - Matthews, George Andrew (d. 1917), "The Vital Force", 1869 (Reel 28)
    - Merrill, John Nelson (d. 1913), "Inflammation", 1869 (Reel 29)
    - Merritt, Sylvester Woodruff (d. 1917), "Diphtheria", 1869 (Reel 29)
    - Merry, John Whiting (d. 1920), "The Red Corpuscle of the Blood", 1869 (Reel 29)
    - Mills, Seth, "Nutrition, Normal and Abnormal", 1869 (Reel 29)
    - Morrison, Peter James, "Typhoid Fever", 1869 (Reel 29)
    - Mulheron, John Jolliffe (d. 1913), "Pain", 1869 (Reel 29)
    - Neal, James Clinton Mari (d. 1895), "Galen", 1869 (Reel 29)
    - Owen, Frank King (d. 1905), "Typhoid Fever" [degree granted in 1872], 1869 (Reel 29)
    - Packard, David Morgan (d. 1904), "Objections to Medicine as a Science-Considered", 1869 (Reel 29)
    - Palmer, Denham Darius (d. 1908), "Typhoid Fever", 1869 (Reel 29)
    - Palmer, Emmet Newton (d. 1917), "Malignant Growths or Cancer", 1869 (Reel 29)
    - Patterson, Philo David (d. 1903), "Scarlatina", 1869 (Reel 29)
    - Patton, Isaac Marshall (d. 1877), "Gastralgia", 1869 (Reel 29)
    - Peare, Robert John (d. 1907), "Inflammation", 1869 (Reel 29)
    - Pratt, Willis Horton (d. 1910), "The Brain", 1869 (Reel 29)
    - Priest, Daniel Mahlon (d. 1921), "Pathology of Inflammation", 1869 (Reel 30)
    - Quinn, Henry R. (d. 1876), "Cerebro-Spinal Meningitis", 1869 (Reel 30)
    - Rhea, William M. (d. 1899), "Miasmata", 1869 (Reel 30)
    - Rogers, William (d. 1897), "The Blood", 1869 (Reel 30)
    - Rorick, Estell H. (d. 1922), "The Causes of Disease", 1869 (Reel 30)
    - Rouse, William Henry (d. 1889), "Carcinoma", 1869 (Reel 30)
    - Russell, Isaac Wadhams (d. 1876), "Renal and Cystic Calculi", 1869 (Reel 30)
    - Scott, James Greenfield, "Icterus or Jaundice", 1869 (Reel 30)
    - Seymour, Christopher (d. 1917), "Cell-Action", 1869 (Reel 30)
    - Shepard, Allen Avery (d. 1876), "Is Alcohol a Food?", 1869 (Reel 30)
    - Shoff, Oscar Fitz-Allen, "Digitalis", 1869 (Reel 30)
    - Short, William Henry (d. 1920), "Intermittent Fever", 1869 (Reel 30)
    - Snyder, George Washington, "Diphtheria", 1869 (Reel 30)
    - Spalding, Frederick Austin (d. 1895), "Pneumonia", 1869 (Reel 30)
    - Spear, Lloyd Elwin (d. 1907), "Variola", 1869 (Reel 30)
    - Stevens, Merari Benajah (d. 1916), "Pathology of Dropsy", 1869 (Reel 30)
    - Thompson, Wilbur Riley (d. 1922), "Puerperal Eclampsia", 1869 (Reel 30)
    - Thorne, Hiram Smith, "A Retrospect of Medicine", 1869 (Reel 30)
    - Thorp, Elliott Gove (d. 1895), "Tuberculosis Pulmonalis", 1869 (Reel 30)
    - Tindall, Oscar North (d. 1909), "Scrofula", 1869 (Reel 31)
    - Tull, Edward Norris, "Epilepsy", 1869 (Reel 31)
    - Turner, Horace Jerome, "Typhoid Fever", 1869 (Reel 31)
    - Vail, George Nelson (d. 1920), "Pneumonia", 1869 (Reel 31)
    - Van Velsor, Elijah Phelps (d. 1880), "Circulation", 1869 (Reel 31)
    - Young, William, "Transfusion", 1869 (Reel 31)
  - Class of 1870
    - Adair, George William, "The Capillaries", 1870 (Reel 31)
    - Ambrook, Charles (d. 1911), "The Nervous System", 1870 (Reel 31)
    - Beebe, Caspar Volney (d. 1896), "Dysentery", 1870 (Reel 31)
    - Bell, George Mathias (d. 1910), "Miasmatic Fevers", 1870 (Reel 31)
    - Bistline, George Wellington (d. 1903), "Circulation of the Blood", 1870 (Reel 31)
    - Bixler, Samuel Henry Clay (d. 1914), "Acute Pneumonia", 1870 (Reel 31)